good morning guys good morning good
morning good morning
um today i'm going to do a review i just
got the shower
i'm going to do a review on um
my rose gold brightening facial
treatment mask that i got
from my summer fab fit fun box
um if you watched my video i was so
excited and i was said i said i was
going to share with you guys and i am
and here we go so like i said this is my
first time using this
um i'm going to be just as confused if
you guys haven't used it my hair
is a mess
complete mess and you can see i
all natural hair no products but it's a
mess
so okay this is what it is and this
is the instructions on the back you see
it has several different
faces um
i'm going to let me see clint's skin
thoroughly
okay let me do that first
let me rinse my face and okay face is
all
clean which it was before i just did it
over
all right so i guess i'll open this
okay it says cleanse face and then it
says remove
remove protective film on both sides
apply the middle sheet i can't see it
i'm reading like a preschooler but bear
with me i do wear glasses
um okay i can't see okay
face keeping the eye and mouth okay
okay guys here i go
see how it comes out
this is how it looks i'm going to open
it up
it's really really moist and wet
this is the face
so oh gosh i don't want to drop it
i'll show y'all every step okay
so i'm taking this off
yes this was the lit part up it dropped
okay
it smells so good
okay this is the lip
take that off and i guess i gotta pop
out the eyes
this is one eye
this is another eye
okay now
i'm gonna take it off of here
don't take off the nose area
oh my god it smells
so good okay here it is
okay i'm gonna put it on my face
this feels oh my goodness guys like when
i say
so good and smell so good
so i'm i'm evening it out on my face
i'm trying to really like even it but
okay
okay all right this is how this is the
most
flat as i'm going to get it guys
oh my goodness it feels so good you can
actually
feel it doing something to your skin
at this oh goodness
it's really really soft so it can rip at
any time
so you definitely have to be like really
really careful
but yeah guys look at this
so i guess i keep this on my face for a
while um
it says leave on for 20 minutes
so i'm going to do the 20 minute mark
and i'll be back guys and i'll pull it
off
and tell you guys how my skin feels
right now it it i'm like
loving this mess right now you guys get
a good look at it
it's like on my whole face which is
beautiful
my lips is a little it's a little
crooked on here but it's okay
so yeah i'm gonna do my 10 minute mark
and then i will return
don't go nowhere guys i shall return
bye-bye hey guys i'm back it's been 20
minutes you heard the bell i hope you
heard the bells i was really loud but
it's been 20 minutes and i'm still
looking like
anna fell off like one of them like
uh um uh astronaut ships
in the sky and then i'm here like
yeah but anyway i'm about to take it off
and it says when i take it off
i can do my regular um
routine that i usually do with my skin
so and it says like when i take it off
like i can still i can pat it
i can pat my skin um to
for the moisturizer to like really be on
air but when i say
my skin feels good right now it feels
clean
when i first put on i couldn't talk as
much so it's really like
absorbed to my skin like to my face
so yeah it actually feel good it's
lightweight it's
airy it's not hot um
i feel like extra clean if they have one
for like my whole body
i would definitely put it on my whole
body so
all right let's get to it let's take it
off
i'm gonna pull it off from the top
when i say it got on my lip yuck
so i took it off the mask is like this
all right
my face is so
can y'all see how moisture like you can
see it
it feels so good it feels fresh
clean it's like a little breeze
coming from somewhere and i have like no
windows open so that's
it just feels so good so yeah guys
i love it i'll definitely do it again
i'll do it like probably
twice a week because
i don't think you need to do it that
much i'll do like twice a week
but i i definitely recommend you guys to
purchase this it's
it's everything it's all that
so yeah guys it was the rose gold
brightening facial treatment mask
um i got it out of my fabfitfun box
um i don't know where you can purchase
it at
but i will put my um link down below for
fab fit fun but otherwise than that yes
guys i love this so much
and um yeah
so thank you for tuning in thanks for
subscribing
huh and i'm on my road to 300
subscribers guys i'm so excited
so definitely help me out share this
video like this video
and more subscribers i'm on the road to
300 guys i'm
so so happy but yeah stay tuned for more
videos
love you guys live laugh love and stay
blessed
bye bye